<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
                  xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
  <ID>Living Planet</ID>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LT_VISION_REALM</ID>
    <Name>Vision Realm</Name>
    <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>
    <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_VISION_REALM_ENTER</ID>
      <Text>I woke up in a void filled with stars after losing consciousness. A strange white crystal, a couple other glowing crystals, and this system's Sun were also there.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
    
    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_VISION_REALM_DEATH</ID>
      <Text>The stars started to disappear until the Sun was the only remaining star. Shortly afterwards the Sun also died, leaving me in complete darkness.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LT_STRANGE_HOUSE</ID>
    <Name>Strange House</Name>
    <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_STRANGE_HOUSE_ENTER</ID>
      <Text>A lone house on the pole of the planet. There is a hole in the floor that leads to a dark cave.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_HEART</ID>
    <Name>Crystal Heart</Name>
    <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_HEART_TUNNEL</ID>
      <SourceID>LT_STRANGE_HOUSE</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Dark Tunnel</RumorName>
      <Text>I found a cave underneath a house that appears to lead further underground.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_HEART_FIND</ID>
      <Text>A strange, white crystal in a large chamber at the center of the planet. It emits a signal on the Electromagnetic Waves frequency.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <Entry>
      <ID>LT_HEART_INTERFACE</ID>
      <Name>Crystal Interface</Name>
      <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>
      <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>LT_HEART_INTERFACE_FIND</ID>
        <Text>A pillar of crystal emerged from the ground after I entered the room. The Crystal Heart started transmitting some sort of data into the pillar.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>
      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>LT_HEART_INTERFACE_VISION</ID>
        <Text>When I walked into the stream of data, it showed me a vision of what looked like the past and the future.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_WORKSHOP</ID>
    <Name>Crystal Workshop</Name>
    <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_WORKSHOP_TUNNEL</ID>
      <SourceID>LT_CRYSTAL_HEART</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Dark Tunnel</RumorName>
      <Text>I saw a dark tunnel leading out of the central chamber marked by a cairn with a crystal.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_WORKSHOP_ENTER</ID>
      <Text>An old building filled with machinery and crystals. There are a couple crystals that are cut and placed in containers.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_WORKSHOP_LANTERN</ID>
      <Text>I found a lantern in the corner by some drawings. The drawings show someone lighting the lantern by pointing it at either a fire or the sun.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_ENERGIZER</ID>
    <Name>Strange Device</Name>
    <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_ENERGIZER_TUNNEL</ID>
      <SourceID>LT_CRYSTAL_HEART</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Dark Tunnel</RumorName>
      <Text>I saw a dark tunnel leading out of the central chamber marked by a cairn with a circle of lines.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_ENERGIZER_ENTER</ID>
      <Text>An old building with a strange table in the center.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_ENERGIZER_USAGE</ID>
      <Text>I found some drawings on the wall showing someone placing a crystal on the table. The crystal then starts glowing.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_ENERGIZER_USED</ID>
      <Text>When I placed an unlit crystal on the table, it began to glow.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LT_RITUAL_RECORDS</ID>
    <Name>Records Building</Name>
    <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_RECORDS_TUNNEL</ID>
      <SourceID>LT_CRYSTAL_HEART</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Dark Tunnel</RumorName>
      <Text>I saw a dark tunnel leading out of the central chamber marked by a cairn with a book.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_RECORDS_ENTER</ID>
      <Text>An old building filled with papers and books.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_RECORDS_DOOR</ID>
      <Text>There is a locked door at the back of the building. There is an empty socket near it that has a drawing of a glowing lantern.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_RECORDS_RITUAL</ID>
      <Text>I found a strange diagram behind the locked door. It showed three glowing crystals- red, blue, and purple- in three different shapes surrounding a large circle.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</ID>
    <Name>Ritual Chamber</Name>
    <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>
    <IsCuriosity/>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER_TUNNEL</ID>
      <SourceID>LT_CRYSTAL_HEART</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Dark Tunnel</RumorName>
      <Text>I saw a dark tunnel leading out of the central chamber marked by a cairn with three circles.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER_ENTER</ID>
      <Text>An old building with a large table at the center. The table has a large circle in the center surrounded by a 5-sided shape, a 6-sided shape, and a 7-sided shape.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER_USAGE</ID>
      <Text>I found a drawing on the wall showing someone placing an item in the center of the table. The three shapes surrounding the center circle have labels that I can't read. The item that was placed in the center then appears to glow.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>
</AstroObjectEntry>