<AstroObjectEntry xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
                  xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Outer-Wilds-New-Horizons/new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/shiplog_schema.xsd">
  <ID>Shimmering Heart</ID>
  <Entry>
    <ID>LT_STRANGE_HOUSE</ID>
    <Name>Strange House</Name>
    <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_STRANGE_HOUSE_ENTER</ID>
      <Text>A lone house on the pole of the planet. There is a hole in the floor that leads to a dark cave.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_HEART</ID>
    <Name>Crystal Heart</Name>
    <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_HEART_TUNNEL</ID>
      <SourceID>LT_STRANGE_HOUSE</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Dark Tunnel</RumorName>
      <Text>I found a cave underneath a house that appears to lead further underground.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_HEART_FIND</ID>
      <Text>A strange, white crystal in a large chamber at the center of the planet. It emits a signal on the Electromagnetic Waves frequency.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <Entry>
      <ID>LT_HEART_INTERFACE</ID>
      <Name>Crystal Interface</Name>
      <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>
      <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>

      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>LT_HEART_INTERFACE_FIND</ID>
        <Text>A pillar of crystal emerged from the ground after I entered the room. The Crystal Heart started transmitting some sort of data into the pillar.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>
      <ExploreFact>
        <ID>LT_HEART_INTERFACE_VISION</ID>
        <Text>When I walked into the stream of data, it showed me a vision of what looked like the past and the future.</Text>
      </ExploreFact>
    </Entry>
  </Entry>
  
  <Entry>
    <ID>LT_VISION_REALM</ID>
    <Name>Vision Realm</Name>
    <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>
    <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_VISION_REALM_ENTER</ID>
      <Text>I woke up in a void filled with stars after losing consciousness. The Crystal Heart, a strange diagram of shapes, and this system's sun were arranged on a floating platform.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_VISION_REALM_DEATH</ID>
      <Text>The stars started to disappear until the Sun was the only remaining star. Shortly afterwards the Sun also died, leaving me in complete darkness.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_VISION_REALM_BRIDGE</ID>
      <Text>I found a long bridge spanning across the void. At the end of the bridge I saw a glowing door.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_VISION_REALM_TRANSPORTATION</ID>
      <Text>When I placed the lantern on the strange table with the three crystals, it appeared in the void with me.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_WORKSHOP</ID>
    <Name>Crystal Workshop</Name>
    <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_WORKSHOP_TUNNEL</ID>
      <SourceID>LT_CRYSTAL_HEART</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Dark Tunnel</RumorName>
      <Text>I saw a dark tunnel leading out of the central chamber marked by a cairn with a crystal.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_WORKSHOP_ENTER</ID>
      <Text>An old building that looks like it was used for refining crystals. There is a green crystal and a blue crystal on a pallet in the corner.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_WORKSHOP_SYMBOLS</ID>
      <Text>I found four colored symbols on the wall: a red group of three lines, a blue circle with three dots in it, a green square with a line through it, and a purple Y-shaped symbol.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_WORKSHOP_LANTERN</ID>
      <Text>I found a lantern next to some drawings. The drawings show a lit candle being blown out by the wind, then a lit lantern resisting the wind.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_ENERGIZER</ID>
    <Name>Strange Device</Name>
    <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_ENERGIZER_TUNNEL</ID>
      <SourceID>LT_CRYSTAL_HEART</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Dark Tunnel</RumorName>
      <Text>I saw a dark tunnel leading out of the central chamber marked by a cairn with a circle of lines.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_ENERGIZER_ENTER</ID>
      <Text>A worn down building with a strange pedestal on the second floor. The pedestal has a small label showing a regular crystal beginning to glow.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_ENERGIZER_FUNCTION</ID>
      <Text>I found a drawing next to the pedestal that shows a glowing crystal communicating with the Crystal Heart.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_CRYSTAL_ENERGIZER_USED</ID>
      <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
      <Text>When I placed an unlit crystal on the table, it began to glow and started emitting a signal on the Electromagnetic Waves frequency.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LT_RITUAL_RECORDS</ID>
    <Name>Records Building</Name>
    <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>
    <AltPhotoCondition>LT_RITUAL_RECORDS_RITUAL</AltPhotoCondition>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_RECORDS_TUNNEL</ID>
      <SourceID>LT_CRYSTAL_HEART</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Dark Tunnel</RumorName>
      <Text>I saw a dark tunnel leading out of the central chamber marked by a cairn with a book.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_RECORDS_ENTER</ID>
      <Text>An old building filled with writing tablets.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_RECORDS_DOOR</ID>
      <Text>There is a locked door at the back of the building at the bottom of a staircase. A tablet at the top of the staircase shows a drawing of a light that is crossed out.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_RECORDS_CRYSTALS</ID>
      <Text>I found a diagram showing three glowing crystals in three different shapes. It also shows a checkmark next to a drawing of a glowing crystal and an X next to a drawing of a regular crystal.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_RECORDS_RITUAL</ID>
      <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
      <Text>I found a strange diagram behind the locked door. It showed three symbols in three shapes: a series of lines in a pentagon, a circle with three dots in a hexagon, and a strange Y-shaped symbol in a septagon.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>

  <Entry>
    <ID>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</ID>
    <Name>Ritual Chamber</Name>
    <Curiosity>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER</Curiosity>
    <IsCuriosity/>

    <RumorFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER_TUNNEL</ID>
      <SourceID>LT_CRYSTAL_HEART</SourceID>
      <RumorName>Dark Tunnel</RumorName>
      <Text>I saw a dark tunnel leading out of the central chamber marked by a cairn with three circles.</Text>
    </RumorFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER_ENTER</ID>
      <Text>A relatively intact building with a large table at the center. The table has a circle in the center surrounded by 3 different shapes.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER_TABLE</ID>
      <Text>I found a drawing on a wall next to the large table. It shows the layout of the table with 4 labeled areas: the large circle at the center, a pentagon, a hexagon, and a septagon.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>

    <ExploreFact>
      <ID>LT_RITUAL_CHAMBER_SOLUTION</ID>
      <IgnoreMoreToExplore/>
      <Text>When I placed three specific crystals in a circle around an item, the item started emitting a signal on the same frequency as the crystals.</Text>
    </ExploreFact>
  </Entry>
</AstroObjectEntry>